SOHYEON JEON



SOHYEONCLAIRE@GMAIL.COM



+82 010-4403-9233



WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/SHJ021



PORTFOLIO

HTTPS://SITES.GOOGLE.COM/VIEW/3DPR OIECT2-SH

HTTPS://SITES.GOOGLE.COM/VIEW/3DPR
OIECT1-SH

OBJECTIVE

Enthusiastic and productive scientist with years of experiences in Deep Learning, Machine Learning, and Image Processing, as well as in Data Analysis. I'm confident that my skills and knowledge will help your company achieve business goals and be more profitable.

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCHER / KOREA INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

2019.11-2021.08

- 2D single image to 3D reconstruction
- Deep learning with Mask R-CNN and GAN
- Image processing using semi-supervised learning algorithms (computer-assisted annotation, interpolation, alignment)
 - Algorithm development for image data analysis
 - Object detection, Image segmentation, and categorization
- Create high resolution micro/mesoscale brain map annotated dataset using Microsoft CoCo
 - Neuron modeling and neural mechanism simulation
 - Study on Compressed sensing theory and generating point cloud

RESEARCH ASSISTANT / SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL

2018.09-2019.01

- Performed an experiment for patients with dementia
- Assisted in human experiments and analyzed acquired data

RESEARCH ASSISTANT / SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY 2017.06-2018.12

- Conducted a behavioral experiment and analyzed acquired data
- Performed a spatial orientation experiment for human subjects using VR machine
 - Investigated the perceptual ability of bilingual children using EEG
- Assisted in the development of research protocols and procedures

SAMSUNG INT'L HOTEL MANAGEMENT AGENT / HOTEL SHILLA

2013.10-2014.04

SKILLS

PYTHON, TENSORFLOW, PYTORCH, OPENCV, BASH SCRIPTING, LINUX MYSQL, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, MATLAB, DOCKER, GIT, HADOOP, ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR, ADOBE PHOTOSHOP, MS OFFICE - Management in contracts with the hotels in U.S.

- Business trip arrangement and support for the executives in Samsung Group

EDUCATION

MS.C. IN COGNITIVE SCIENCE / AUG 2019

Seoul National University GPA: 3.87 / 4.5

Thesis: An Event-Related fMRI Study of Bilingual Lexical Processing and Cross-linguistic Interaction

B.A. IN PHISOLOPHY / FEB 2017

Kyunghee University GPA: 3.02 / 4.5

PRESENTATIONS

POSTER PRESENTER / BRAIN SCIENCE INSTITUTE SYMPOSIUM

2020.12.09-12.10
Title: Building Digital Atlas from Scratch

POSTER PRESENTER / BRAIN SCIENCE INSTITUTE SYMPOSIUM

2019.12.05-12.06 Title: Annotating Brain with Atlas

POSTER PRESENTER / INTERNATIONAL BRAIN RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (IBRO)

2019.09/24-09.25

Title: Bilingual Lexical Processing and Cross-linguistic Interaction: A Behavioral and fMRI Study

COURSES

PYTORCH ESSENTIAL TRAINING: DEEP LEARNING

2020.11 / LINKEDIN

DEEP LEARNING: IMAGE RECOGNITION

2020.11 / LINKEDIN

INTRODUCTION TO DEEP LEARNING WITH OPENCY

2020.12 / LINKEDIN

TRAINING NEURAL NETWORKS IN PYTHON

2020.12 / LINKEDIN

ADVANCED PYTHON

2020.11 / LINKEDIN

BUILDING TOOLS WITH PYTHON

2020.11 / LINKEDIN

PYTHON DATA STRUCTURE AND ALGORITHMS

2020.12 / LINKEDIN

PYTHON DATA STRUCTURES: LINKED LISTS

2020.12 / LINKEDIN

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

COGNITIVE SCIENCE INSTRUCTOR / DAEWON FOREIGN LANGUAGE HIGH SCHOOL

2018.05.24

INTERN / MERCURE SYDNEY

2010.08-2011.02

PARTICIPATED PROJECTS

DEVELOPMENT OF THE ALGORITHM AND THE COMPUTATIONAL MODEL OF CEREBELLAR INFORMATION PROCESSING BASED ON STATE-OF-THE-ART NEUROSCIENCE

2021.04-2021.08 KOREA INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

AI-NEURAL NETWORK RESEARCH TO PREDICT AND OVERCOME BRAIN DISEASES

2021.01-2021.08 KOREA INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

COMPREHENSIVE STRUCTURAL MAPPING & A INTEGRATIVE DB CONSTRUCTION OF BASAL GANGLIA CIRCUITS RELATED TO NEUROLOGICAL DISORDERS

2019.11-2021.08 KOREA INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

INTEGRATED STRUCTURAL AND FUNCTIONAL MAPPING OF NEURAL CIRCUITS USING THE SMART-AR MICROSCOPE

2019.11-2021.08 KOREA INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

MULTISENSORY INTERACTION FOR PERCEPTUAL CATEGORIZATION AND SPATIAL ORIENTATION

2017.07-2018.12 SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

NEURAL MECHANISMS AND INTERACTION OF MOTOR EFFERENCE AND SENSORY FEEDBACK

2017.06-2018.12 SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY